well let's see
bueno a ver
and It's that today I don't know if we should set goals for
e Es que hoy no sé si poner objetivos al
Anne It's that today I do
Anne Es que hoy no sé si poner objetivos
n't know if we should set goals eh I don't know if we should set a goal today I think that
eh No sé si poner objetivo hoy Yo creo
today no I think that today we're not going to
que hoy no yo creo que hoy no vamos a
set a goal But not for nothing but
poner objetivo Pero no por nada sino
because if I set a goal for Super chat
porque si pongo objetivo de Super chat
people won't become members no I mean
la gente no se hace miembro no O sea
today I prefer that people become members
prefiero hoy que que la gente se haga
no and that they try a little not to
miembro no y que intenten un poco no
get too close to what happened yesterday with the kids
acercarse a lo de ayer de la chavalería
to tell them something later when I
para decirles algo luego cuando yo
arrive no like the ass I wouldn't
llegue no cómo lo al asne Yo hoy no
set a goal today but rather whoever wants
pondría objetivo sino que quien quiera
whoever wants can do it with
que quien quiere pueda que lo haga con
members today not with super chat what does
miembros hoy no con super chat qué tiene
age have to do with it they always throw you out for
que ver la edad a ti te tiran siempre
age and we get
por lo de la edad y nosotros nos
angry about that man uki well age
enojamos por eso hombre uki pues la edad
has a lot to do with it let's see they always throw you out
tiene mucho que ver a ver a ti te tiran
for age to me when they tell me
siempre por la edad a mí cuando me dicen
something about age it's like you can't gossip
algo de la edad es no puedes hacer
because you're 40 years old it's you can't
salseo porque tienes 40 años es no puede
do salt that I'm 40 years old it's an
hac sal que tenga 40 años es una cosa
illogical thing Now what's not illogical
ilógica Ahora bien lo que no es ilógico
is that when you're a certain age it's
es que cuando tú tienes una edad cierta
okay Because when you're a
edad vale Porque tú cuando eres un
teenager  you can make mistakes And you may have made
adolescente te puedes equivocar Y puede
mistakes and
que te hayas equivocado y hayas hecho
bullied at school, you may have messed
bullying en el instituto te hayas metido
with someone or fallen for these things
con alguien o hayas caído en estas cosas
okay but man that you at 34 years old
vale pero hombre que tú con 34 años te
make fun of a person because they are fat
burles de una persona porque está Gorda
but all because they have other ideas
pero todo porque tiene otras ideas
because you are not really making fun of them
porque no te estás burlando en realidad
Because she is fat because you have a
Porque esté gorda porque tienes un
lot of fat people in your parties okay You
montón de gordos en tus partidos vale Te
are making fun of the girl because she
estás burlando de la chavala porque
has other ideas and because she is going to
tiene otras ideas y porque va a
present the new year's chimes do you
presentar las campanadas
understand me around here we live well
me entiendes por aquí convivimos bien
people from the right and people from the left
gente de derecha y gente de izquierda
So don't [ __ ] with the
Así que no jodáis la
[Music]
[Música]
filthy
marrañero
that no I don't know there are many people who when I
que no no sé hay mucha gente que cuando
say it no they don't understand it But I understand it
lo digo no no lo entiende Pero yo lo
easily I mean no no no it's not that
entiendo facilito O sea no no no es que
I am a fanatic and I defend that party
yo sea fanático y defienda ese partido
no my god don't mess with this
no madre mía no te metas con este
party No no it's that within those that there are you
partido No no es que dentro de los que
know the others seem worse to me and you have to
hay sabes los otros me parecen peores y
vote for some and apart from that what the [ __ ]
hay que votar alguno y aparte que [__]
[ __ ] the truth is my ideas are more
[__] la verdad son mis ideas más
similar you instead of not commenting on this
parecidas tú en vez de no comentar esto
Go on, I'll hit you sea But it's that I don't
Dale que te pego mar Pero es que yo no
have to, I don't have to deprive myself  and there
me tengo que yo no me tengo que privar y
are many people who tell me no don't
yo hay mucha gente que me dicen no no
mention this don't mention this because you
menciones esto no menciones esto porque
divide us or because people get angry
divides o porque la gente se enfada
with you
contigo
I sincerely believe that here we should
Yo es que sinceramente creo que aquí
all be free to
tenemos que ser todos libres para
express ourselves and debate it and the majority
expresarnos y debatirlo y la mayoría de
here are of the weight and things like that and and that's it
aquí soy del peso y cosas de eso y y ya
if we come here to talk about
está si aquí venimos para hablar de
gossip what does it matter you understand we
cotillo qué más da me entiendes nos
respect each other and that's it we can talk about it well
respetamos y ya está lo podemos hablar
no a kid came up yesterday who was
pues no subió ayer un chaval que era
super progressive and we agreed on
super progr y estábamos de acuerdo en
some things and others didn't no that's it what does it matter
algunas cosas y otros no no ya está qué
well I don't know well vote whoever
más da pues yo que sé pues vota quien
wants no Javi you Go for the bun it's
quiera no Javi tú Dale al moño que es
more entertaining Yes let's see about the
más entretenido Sí a ver sobre el tema
bun subject Well my alar has come out or what does
moñe Bueno mi alar ha saído o qué dice
Geena say they bullied me
geena a mí me hicieron bullying en el
because I was brilliant pretty smart and with
porque era brillante guapa lista y con
very good grades Georgina they
buenísimas notas Georgina a mí me lo
did it to me but because I was ugly let's see
hicieron pero porque era feo a ver
bullying I have not been a victim of
bullying tampoco he sido una víctima de
bullying as such but maybe on
bullying como tal pero a lo mejor en
some specific occasion no
alguna ocasión puntual no
eh Let's see is it spelled bully Javi is it true
eh A ver se escribe bully Javi es verdad
[ __ ] well nothing I have already written it it is
[__] pues ya nada ya lo he escrito es
true I should have put bully not
verdad tenía que haber puesto bully no
bullying Okay  I can fix it no almost no
bulling Bueno lo puedo arreglar no casi
one has seen it yet what a
no lo ha visto nadie todavía qué
maniac I am with the
maniático soy con el tema de de la
spelling thing eh on Twitter Twitter man
ortografía eh en en Twitter Twitter tío
Calm down a
Cálmate un
little in fact I think I just got
poco de hecho creo que me acabo de poner
the punctuation wrong too Look it doesn't matter
mal la puntuación también Mira da igual
man Twitter let's see alanne is there Lili
tío Twitter a ver alanne está ahí Lili
Lili alazne has to be counting
Lili alazne tiene que estar contando
to 100 with that lady Okay what's
hasta 100 con la señora esa Bueno lo que
coming is no nonsense eh what's
se viene no es ninguna tontería eh lo
coming today is really difficult eh I
que se viene hoy es tela marinera eh o
mean Loli has been asking for the boycott no
sea Loli ha estado pidiendo el boicot no
Lili I mean I saw your headline but I have
Lili o sea yo he visto tu titular pero
n't seen the cli yet I'm going to
el cli todavía no lo he visto lo voy a
watch it here with
ver aquí con
you Lili we set a goal today or not
ustedes Lili ponemos objetivo hoy o no
today members no today whoever wants members
hoy miembros no hoy quien quiera
no today whoever wants member today
miembros no hoy quien quiera miembro hoy
Super chat goal we're not going to put I
objetivo de Super chat no vamos a poner
think we already have all the Super
creo que ya tenemos todos los Super
chats for the month covered they've been used up there's
chats del mes cubiertos se han gastado
no more room and I think that and I think
no hay más hueco y creo que y creo que
today's goal we're not going to put it is that there
objetivo hoy no vamos a poner es que
should also be a goal that was
debería haber un objetivo también que
members right when it says
fuera de miembros verdad cuando pone
here goal select a goal there
aquí objetivo selecciona un objetivo
should be a goal that was
debería haber un objetivo que fuera de
members also bad thought YouTube
miembros también mal pensado YouTube
Loli has had an allergy
Loli ha tenido alergia otra
again well let's see I don't know if there will  it's been an
vez bueno a ver no sé si habrá sido cosa
allergy thing But the truth is that it's
de la alergia Pero la verdad es que se
gone eh it's gone it's gone it's
le ha ido eh se le ha ido se le ha ido
gone each Spaniard but not to me they have to
ido cada españ pero no a m a d tienen
touch your nose they take
que tócate las narices sacan de contexto
alazne's comment out of context I'm saturated
el comentario de alazne estoy saturada
with shorts Ah so it comes from something
de cortos Ah o sea que viene por una
taken out of context let's see what
sacada de contexto a ver a mí lo que me
Lili tells me is that it all comes from this
dice Lili es que todo viene por este
clip of this anarchy clown one day
clip del payaso este de anarquía un día
I have to do a live solo of
tengo que hacer un directo solo de
anarchy man comparing one thing
anarquía tío comparando e lo unas cosas
with another What happens is that this one will have
con otras Lo que pasa que este tendrá
half half Twitter deleted by now he will have
medio medio Twitter borrado ya tendrá
half Twitter deleted by now let's see
medio Twitter borrado ya a ver a mí me
Lili told me that she comes for this alanne
ha dicho Lili que viene por esto alanne
In key in the live of the youtuber Neo
En clave en el directo del youtuber Neo
programat trix Neo programat
programat trix Neo programat pasan
bank cards pass through my hands and I
cartillas bancarias por mis manos y yo
see what these people charge for help And it
veo lo que cobra esta gente de ayuda Y
embarrasses me he talks about taking the
me da vergüenza habla de que sacan el
money out and depositing it in another account and he
dinero y lo ingresan en otra cuenta y
says all this publicly you see it
todo esto lo dice públicamente lo veis
normal luckily unfortunately
normal por suerte por desgracia pasan
many bank cards pass through my hands in the
muchas cartillas bancarias por mis manos
end true I see true Lili I have to
cabo verdad yo veo verdad Lili lo tengo
hair let's see if I have time  that
que hair a ver si tengo tiempo lo que
these people charge for aid and it
cobra esta gente de ayudas y me
hurts me But what's the problem The right
daza Pero cuál es el problema El derecho
to privacy and PR
a la intimidad y la PR
but it's not violating anything they're not
pero no está vulnerando nada no está
telling anyone what they charge in
diciéndole lo que cobra nadie en
particular it's very general I'm
concreto es muy en general me da
ashamed of what I see that they charge for
vergüenza lo que veo que cobran de
aid that according to they make the deposit that
ayudas que según le hacen el ingreso ese
same day or the next day they take out all
mismo día o al día siguiente sacan todo
the money they put it
el dinero
in another unmonitored account
íntegro lo meten en otra cuenta no
because Of course the moment
vigilada porque Claro en el momento en
they see that they are spending 300
el que viesen que se están gastando 300
or 400 on telephone
o 400 en telefonía
aid but in other words what's the move
las ayudas pero o sea cuál es la movida
of anarchy instead of criticizing what
de anarquía en vez de criticar lo que
alanne is saying or rather those who do
está contando alanne o sea los que hacen
the things that alanne is saying
las cosas que está contando alanne la
she criticizes her for saying it This is
critica ella por contarlo Es que esto es
wonderful this is like what Tania did
maravilloso esto es como lo de Tania
this is like with Tania instead of
esto es como con lo de Tania en vez de
criticizing that Tania was defending
criticar que Tania estuviera defendiendo
man my Dolores Look at my Dolores as she
hombre mi Dolores Mira mi Dolores como
comes in she says hello Javi Good night
entra ya dice hola Javi Buenas noches
handsome dolores hasn't made you a member
guapetón dolores no te ha hecho miembro
dolores Look at dolores Look at the kids
dolores Mira dolores Mira la chavalería
43 members and so much here Today without a member
43 miembros y tato aquí Hoy sin miembro
And you continue  voting for Pedro Sanchez which
Y sigues votando a Pedro Sánchez que
also needs to be mentioned because like
también hay que comentarlo pues como
any person who works in a
cualquier persona que trabaja en un
bank, it goes through his hand, of course, let's
banco pasa por su mano hombre claro a
see, let's see the bank, imagine one from a
ver a ver del banco imagínate uno de un
bank in Andorra, okay, the buffoon of
banco de andorra vale el bufón de
anarchy. No, he's not a total buffoon, eh, I
anarquía No no es un bufón total eh o
mean, imagine one from a bank in Andorra,
sea imagínate uno de un banco de andorra
one who is in the cash register of the bank of Andorra.
un uno que está en la caja del banco
Okay, and he takes it and says [ __ ], well,
andorra Vale y coge y dice [__] pues
what the youtubers earn passes through my hands
por mis manos pasan lo que cobran los
and don't you see what the
youtubers y no ve a lo que cobran los
sio [ __ ] earn, but that has nothing to do with it,
sio [__] Pero eso no tiene nada que ver
my god, you know, Javi, I promise you that
madre mía Sabes Javi te prometo que
when he arrives and visa I become a member,
cuando llega y visa me hago miembro
Dolores, I don't know if I can trust Dolores, I don't know if I can
dolores no sé si fiarme dolores no sé si
trust Dolores, someone can give him
fiarme dolores alguien le puede regalar
a member, Dolores, and he says. That's
un miembro dolores y dice Eso sí es
true. There I can't lie to you,
verdad Ahí sí que no te puedo mentir
but Dolores, I would love for you to come up
pero dolores Me encantaría que subieras
one day to do an interview with you about
un día para hacerte una entrevista sobre
Pedro Sanchez, listen to me, let's
Pedro Sánchez escúchame vamos a
see one. Imagine, no, one from a bank in
ver una imaginaros no Uno de un banco de
Andorra who works in a bank and takes it and
andorra que trabaja en un banco y coge y
says [ __ ], the
dice [__] yo por mis manos pasan las
booklets of these people pass through my hands and such and I know
cartillas de esta gente y tal y sé lo
what  they charge a lot and don't see what they charge
que cobran mucho y no ve a lo que cobran
just no I mean it doesn't say who or
sin más no O sea ni dice quién ni dice
how much or when I mean it doesn't say anything
cuánto ni dice cuándo O sea no dice nada
then eh I or I mean I've seen how they
entonces eh yo le o sea he visto como lo
take it out of one account and put it into another in
sacan de una cuenta la meten en otra a
another person's name which is the one they
nombre de otra persona que es por la que
pass the phone bill through and they
le pasan la factura de la telefonía y
have 100 lines on all the lines
tienen 100 líneas en todas las líneas
Javi Set a goal go on that
Javi Pon objetivo anda que Mola mucho la
WhatsApp is really cool that we have with that
WhatsApp que nos traemos con eso
but today I want them to make
pero es que hoy quiero que hagan
members not to compete with the
miembros no para competir con la
kids It's not that if I set a goal
chavalería No es que si pongo objetivo
if the gang gets a kiss Isabel beautiful
si la peña se pone un beso Isabel guapa
Look Isabel has given one away it's that
Mira Isabel ha regalado uno es que
we have 72 members I mean I think
llevamos 72 miembros o sea yo creo que
if I set a goal for Super chat they are not going to
si pongo objetivo de Super chat no van a
give members or I mean the same as they are going to
dar miembros o sea lo mismo que vayan a
give in super chat that they give it in membership
dar en super chat que lo den en miembro
and for me Javi who has gray hair in
y a mí Javi que me ha salido canas en
unexpected places waiting for membership
sitios insospechados esperando membresía
Carmen Carmen Miguel Ramiro wants you to
Carmen Carmen Miguel Ramiro quiere que
give her a membership come on
le regalis una membresía venga va
as long as you don't give names or surnames
mientras no de nombres ni apellidos clo
exactly I mean it's as if I say what I'll
exactamente o sea es como si yo digo qué
tell you the example that I have given you the
Te digo yo el ejemplo que os he puesto
Andorran it's not like if I
la andorrano no es como si os
tell you a doctor
digo un médico
eh a doctor who does an interview
eh un médico que le hacen una entrevista
on a YouTube channel with the doctor and the
en un canal de YouTube al médico y el
doctor goes on and comments man there are many
médico coge y comenta hombre hay mucha
people who come with that they come with
gente que viene con que viene con
pregnancies you know and then I ask them and it
embarazos sabes y luego les pregunto y
turns out that they have not used any
resulta que no han utilizado medios de
protection measures, they are not counting who is
protección no está contando quién está
counting you know no they cannot be
contando sabes no no se puede
identified I mean
identificar O sea que no tiene sentido
the right to privacy doesn't make sense and
el derecho a la intimidad y la
privacy gives you the
privacidad te pone con Smartphone del
top of the range smartphone that is available at that time and
tope de gama que haya en ese momento y
then you see that they are giving them help
luego ves que les están dando ayudas
for the house for water for electricity
para la casa para el agua para la luz
they pay for their school they give them free
les pagan el colegio les regalan los
medicines they have priority at the
medicamentos tienen prioridad en en el
doctor
médico
eh they give them the weekly shopping and they are
eh les dan la compra semanal y se están
spending 300 and 400 on high-end phones my
gastando 300 y 400 en teléfonos de alta
head explodes when I see
a mí me explota la cabeza Cuando veo
those
esas
things but this is not talked about a kiss
cosas pero de esto no se habla un beso
in Thank you very much welcome handsome and it's not anymore he
en Muchísimas gracias bienvenido guapo y
says as if as if you work
ya no es dice como si como si trabajaras
in an insurance company and you know how much
En una compañía de seguros y supieras la
money people spend on cars of
pasta que se gasta la gente en coches
course I know you don't As long as you don't say
claro se que no Mientras que no digas
who how much and
quién cuánto Y
how but apart from that now I'm going to explain something
cómo pero aparte ahora os voy a explicar
else have you had any job that  you will
otra cosa has tenido algún trabajo que
deeply hate the one I have right now
profundamente el que tengo ahora
Mariluz has given one a kiss
mismo Mariluz ha regalado uno un beso
Thank you very much you see Lili you see I mean I
Muchas gracias lo ves Lili lo ves O sea
prefer today of members to see
yo prefiero hoy día de miembros a ver
how the kids do it
cómo lo hace la chavalería la
[Music]
[Música]
gentlemen it's my kids
señoreros es mi chavalería
yesterday this is my kids yesterday Peppa
ayer esto es mi chavalería ayer Peppa
works no matter how much she wants to deny it or
funciona por mucho que lo quiera negar o
rather here this person for whatever reason has
sea aquí esta persona por lo que sea se
started taking these screenshots and says
ha puesto a [__] estas capturas y dice
that this is for Peppa and and it's the
que que esto es por Peppa y y es la
salsera But well each one to their joints
salsería Pero bueno cada uno sus porros
no and their things Look at the kids yere
no y sus cosas Mirad la chavalería yere
look at the chat all colors Look Look I
mirar el chat todo colores Mirad Mirad O
mean it didn't make any [ __ ] sense
sea no tenía ningún putísimo sentido
okay King at home we all have your
vale Rey en casa todas tenemos tus
members Hey but That sounds a bit strange
miembros Oye pero Eso suena un poco raro
eh I don't know if I liked it it burns
eh No sé si me ha gustado es que quema
a lot
muchísimo
eh Because it's a continuous pressure and it's
eh Porque es una presión continua y es
a
una presión
continuous pressure from those above on one side and the
continua de los de arriba por un lado y
client on the other I mean you're in
del cliente por otro o sea tú estás en
the middle and you feel continuous pressure from
el medio y sientes presión continua por
both sides Okay then in the
las dos partes Vale entonces al
end psychologically It burns a lot
final psicológicamente Quema mucho
a lot I mean as I
muchísimo O sea ya te
told you I have not had a vacation for many months
digo llevo sin vacaciones muchos meses
so in the end you are tired and and your
entonces al final estás cansado y y tu
mind asks you for a  break I mean I understand
mente te pide un break o sea entiendo
that for those who are taking this
que para los que están sacando este
comment out of context Look, for me this
comentario de contexto Mira para mí esto
would be some kind of harassment, okay, I mean He
sería un tipo de de acoso vale o sea
's taking a clip out of context, who
Está sacando de contexto un clip que
knows, the persecution to
vete tú a saber la persecución para
find something like that, no Because on top of that it
encontrar una cosa así no Porque encima
's a channel that I don't even know what the [ __ ]
es un canal que ni yo sé ni qué [__]
channel is alanne the truth is I don't know where the hell
canal es alanne la verdad no sé dónde
you gave this interview you know but
[__] has dado esta entrevista sabes pero
what you're doing is like promoting you want to
lo que haces es e como promover quieres
promote that someone gets fired from their job, I mean you
promover que la que despidan a una
're not
persona del trabajo o sea ya no estás ni
even insulting a person from the
siquiera insultando a una persona de
networks that you don't like or
redes que te cae mal o
[Music]
[Música]
criticizing you to leave the card of
criticándote para dejar la cartilla de
one of us to Anne even tells
alguno de nosotros al Anne cuenta hasta
how much we spend on
lo que nos gastamos en películas de
rental movies no man you know well her ideology
alquiler no tío sabes bueno su ideología
she has left it more than Clara always I
ella la ha dejado más que Clara siempre
think it will go there she's talking about
creo que irá por ahí está hablando de
the Moroccans and the hoax of the allowances
los marroquí y el bulo de las paguitas
the hoax of the allowances eh it's a hoax no no there are no
el bulo de las paguitas eh es un bulo no
payments eh There are no payments It's a
no no hay pagas eh No hay pagas Es un
hoax
bulo
Oh invasion of privacy says conchi
Ay invasión a la privacidad dice conchi
but it's not even
pero es que ni siquiera es
and crimes are committed there is no crime
e cometen delitos no hay ningún delito
as far as I understand there is
hasta donde yo entiendo ahí no hay
no  crime and you are not Eh you
ningún delito y tú no estás Eh tú no
are not eh
estás eh
revealing anyone's privacy the
revelando la intimidad de nadie el
crime of revealing a secret is a
delito de revelación de Secreto es un
crime that can only be prosecuted by
delito que solamente lo puede perseguir
the person who considers themselves violated, in other
la persona que se considera vulnerada o
words, the crime of revealing a secret is
sea el delito de revelación de Secreto
not pursued by the prosecutor's office, nor is it
no lo persigue la fiscalía ni lo ni lo
pursued ex officio, in other words, it has to be
persigue de oficio o sea tiene que ser
the violated person who
la persona vulnerada la que quiere
also wants to maintain the charge no So
además mantener la el cargo no Entonces
in this case, the person who feels that
en este caso la la persona que se sienta
their privacy, their right
que ha vulnerado su intimidad su derecho
to privacy and privacy has been violated Okay, well, they
a la intimidad y la privacidad Vale pues
are the ones who would have to report it, of course, what
es la que tendría que denunciar claro qu
happens is that who is going to report it
es lo que pasa que quién va a denunciar
if they haven't told you, they haven't told anyone, they said
si no te no ha dicho a nadie ha dicho
that they pass books through their hand and that
que por su mano pasan cartillas y que
she usually sees people, I understand that she is
ella suele ver a gente entiendo que está
talking about immigrants, not those who get
hablando de inmigrantes no a los que le
paid the same day they get
dan una paga el mismo día que cobran la
paid, they take it out and then use it on
paga la la sacan para luego emplearlo en
powerful phones or I don't know what Or I don't know
teléfonos potentes o no sé qué O no sé
how much it is, it doesn't make
cuánto sea es que no tiene sentido
any sense, eh, you don't even know what they are
ninguno eh No sabes ni lo que están
criticizing But we use this
criticando siquiera Pero esto lo usamos
so that Loli now starts to insinuate,
para que Loli ahora se ponga a insinuar
no, eh, that we have to call work  from
no eh que hay que llamar al trabajo de
alanne so they throw her out alanne is
alanne para que la echen alanne está
reporting an incident that happens very
denunciando un hecho que se da con mucha
frequently without names or anything but
frecuencia sin nombres ni nada pero es
instead of criticizing the incident that she is
que en vez de criticar el hecho que está
reporting on Anne okay they criticize
denunciando al Anne vale la critican a
her and start saying that she is
ella y se ponen a decir que está
accusing that she has committed crimes
imputando que que ha cometido delitos
Mara del mar a kiss
María del mar un beso
Oh holy patience things have to be
Ay Santa paciencia las cosas hay que
taken from who always comes to
tomarla de quiin viene siempre a
us this well the laughter and outside
nosotros esto pues las risas y fuera más
no what can I tell you
no qué te digo
or she hears it somewhere else from other
o las escucha en otra parte a otra
people and she joins in she makes up
personas y ella se ha acopla se inventa
stories and things like that okay I can give you
cuentos y cosas así vale Te puedo poner
an example the same I mean imagine that I
1 ejemplos igual O sea imagínate que yo
work at a dealership and for them to
trabajo en un concesionario no Y para
finance your car well you have to
que te financien el coche pues me tienes
give me the latest movements the
que dar los últimos movimientos las
last three paychecks and I get here I
últimas tres nóminas y yo cojo aquí
arrive at night and I say [ __ ] Don't see
llego por la noche y digo [__] No veas
the people man Don't see the people that I see
la gente tío No veas la gente que yo veo
that earn 1000 euros and put
que cobran 1000 eur y se ponen letras de
BMW letters of 500 a month you understand me yeah
bmv de de 500 al mes me entiendes sea
I'm violating anyone's privacy
estoy vulnerando la privacidad de nadie
nor am I violating anyone's privacy it does
ni estoy vulnerando la intimidad es que
n't make any sense dude  it doesn't make
no tiene sentido ninguno tío no tiene
any sense
sentido ninguno
eh And I'm completely sure
eh Y yo estoy completamente seguro de
that but let's see we're
que pero a ver estamos intentando
also trying to make sense of these people you
también Buscar sentido en esta gente
know l has invented many things about
sabes l ha inventado muchas cosas sobre
Peppa and about money that she has given to
Peppa y sobre dinero que le haya dado a
pppa for things and she has started talking
pppa de cosas y se ha puesto a hablar
to people in private the other
por ahí con la gente en privado el otro
day we saw how the detective was already
día vimos como al det ya contaba
completely convinced that Loli
completamente convencido que Loli le
had given 1000 euros to Peppa to
había dado 1000 eur a Peppa por
return the 500 from B that for cto
devolverle los 500 del B que por cto
about that then one
sobre eso cí luego una
thing Look Abi we are
cosa Mira Abi
going to listen to you because you lie and
te vamos a escuchar porque mientes y
all of us who are here plus a lot
todos los que estamos aquí más un montón
who are not know that you lie and what does
que no están saben que mientes y los Qué
my Dolores say about the payments are
dice mi Dolores eso de las pagas son
just lies I know a lot of Moroccans
rollo mentiras yo conozco mucho marroquí
who have worked with me and they don't have any
que ha trabajado conmigo y no tiene
payment none of them are a hoax from those who
ninguna paga ninguno son bulo de los que
vote for you
votan a vos
Hahaha dolores dolores the thing is that the payments are
Jajaja dolores dolores es que las pagas
not about them being Moroccan I mean the
no tratan de que sean mar roqu O sea la
payment is not based on the nationality that
paga no es por la nacionalidad que
you have the payment has certain requirements that
tengas la paga tien unos requisitos que
There will be people who meet them and people who are not
Habrá gente que lo cumple y gente que no
worth it but for example it is a reality
vale pero por ejemplo es una realidad
that when a boat loaded with
que cuando llega una patera cargada de
people who come illegally arrives the
personas que vienen ilegalmente las
They put them in a hotel first, in this case it
meten primero en un hotel en este caso
is from the Canary Islands, no, because they
está siendo de las Canarias no porque
appear there, they put them in
aparecen allí los meten en hoteles de
great hotels and then they take planes and
[__] madre y luego cogen aviones y los
distribute them throughout the Peninsula, we have
reparten por la Península eso lo hemos
seen that, no, that would not be, that would not be
visto no eso no serían eso no serían
aid from public money, okay. And now
ayudas de dinero público vale Y ahora
then you pay them and what corresponds.
luego las pagas y lo que corresponda
Well, that depends on a series of
Pues eso depende de una serie de
requirements, but man, there is
requisitos pero hombre hay un hay como
a minimum, not to live, that if they
un mínimo no para vivir que si te
contribute to you, they have it on another channel that I
aportan lo tienen en otro canal que lo
am going to name, you know, and it is not going to be talked about. I will
voy a nombrar lo sab y no se va falar
tell you my opinion on that
que yo te digo mi opinión respecto a eso
if you want it, eh, for me, they are. I think
si la quieres eh sea para m son yo creo
that first you have to take care of
que primero tienes que tener atendido a
your people and I have no problem with
tu pueblo y yo no tengo ningún problema
people from other countries
en que venga gente de otros países que
coming to work. I have the problem
vengan a trabajar yo tengo el problema
with people who come to commit crimes, you know, I
con gente que venga a delinquir sabes o
mean, I have a problem with
sea yo tengo problema con que venga
people coming to rape, to commit crimes because they have
gente a violar a delinquir porque tien
normalized other things, no. And other
normalizadas otras cosas no Y otros
behaviors, no, that are not civic. And
comportamientos no que no son cívicas Y
then they come, they rape, you know, they steal, you know,
entonces vienen violan sabes roban sabes
those things, no, I
esas cosas no yo tengo problema con eso
have no problem with that, I have had a
tengo ningún problema yo he tenido un
lot of  colleagues at work but it's not
montón de compañeros en el trabajo pero
that I've had colleagues It
no es que he tenido compañeros de
's that I have colleagues
trabajo Es que yo aquí tengo compañeros
from all over the planet, I
de trabajo de todo el planeta o sea yo
mean, I didn't collaborate with a Mexican here yesterday, I don't collaborate with Mexicans, with people from Florida, with people from Miami, with people from Colombia, with people from Peru, or rather, how many people do we collaborate with here, especially on the subject, on the issues of the salsa bar,
en el tema en los temas de la salsería
no. I mean, what does it matter, personally, what I
no O sea qué más da yo personalmente lo
think is worth it is that they use
que pienso vale es que utilizan
supposedly left-wing or
ideologías supuestamente de izquierdas o
progressive ideologies to deceive people who don't
progresistas para engañar a gente que no
care much about whether things are
se preocupa mucho por si las cosas se
fulfilled or not, it's worth it,
cumplen o no vale
and no, no. Look, we're not racists, we
e no no Mira nosotros no somos racistas
take everyone who comes
nosotros cogemos a todos los que vienen
and we give them some aid because,
y y les damos unas ayudas porque
poor thing, because I don't know, I don't know how much it's
Pobrecito porque no sé que no sé cuánto
worth. And no, no, in reality, what they're
vale Y no no en realidad lo que están
doing is gaining votes because the people
haciendo es ganar votos porque la gente
here are not going to vote for them anymore. And so
de aquí ya no les va a votar Y entonces
what they're doing
lo que están haciendo
is bringing potential voters into the country.
son meter en el país potenciales votad
Better said, you know, without further ado. I mean, yes, yes, if
votantes Mejor dicho sabes sin más O sea
you tell me that, Ah,
si si si tú a mí me dices que Ah pasado
a catastrophe like the one that happened in
una catástrofe como la que ha pasado en
Valencia has happened and they don't let people throw it out, I don't
Valencia y no dejan a la gente tirar a
care, eh, or  I'm so happy that they
mí me da igual eh o sea yo tan contento
take half of me away, eh And I'm so
con que me quiten la mitad eh Y yo tan
happy that now an
contento con que ahora venga un
immigrant comes and they give him help so that he
inmigrante y le den una auda para que
can make a new life here,
para que pueda hacer una nueva vida aquí
okay, yes, at the moment that at the
vale eso sí en el momento que en el
moment he commits a crime, to take him where he
momento que delinca a a llevarlo a donde
belongs, you understand, but man, when
pertenezca me entiendes pero hombre que
I see that some things happen and that
yo vea que se dan unas cosas y que se
some resources are spent on some things
gastan unos recursos para unas cosas
when then you have the people here
cuando luego a la gente de aquí la
abandoned living in bacteria,
tienes abandonada viviendo en bacteria
well, the truth is it makes me think Dolores,
pues la verdad me da que pensar Dolores
that Pedro Snchez is only
que a Pedro Sánchez lo único que le
interested in buying votes with our
interesa es comprar votos con nuestro
money but
dinero pero
you lie because I,
mientes porque yo
uh, that morning I got up, I sent him what they
eh esa mañana me levanté le mandé lo que
had sent me, I told him what they had
me habían mandado le dije lo que me
told me, I was pissed off one of my
habían dicho cé un cabreo de Mis
demons and he told me that he was going to
demonios y me dijo que me lo iba a
forward it to me very well, that in the morning
reenviar muy bien eso por la mañana
later, when we were calmer, he would forward it to me
después ya más calmados me lo reenviara
and a live broadcast was opened to say that he had
y se abría un directo para decir que lo
done it, the answer to forward it to me
había hecho la respuesta que me lo
was, Okay, you give me
reenviara era Bueno tú si me tú me das
500, I'll give you 1000, Okay, if you give me
500 yo te doy 1000 Bueno si tú me das
500 then if I want I'll give you 1000 if I
500 luego yo si quiero te doy 1000 si
want I'll give you 1000 And then yes, shortly
quiero te doy 1000 Y entonces sí ya poco
before the live broadcast, that step was taken,
antes del directo se hizo ese ese paso
which since they had already sent it to me
cosa que ya como ya me lo habían enviado
and she already knew that it wasn't valid eh I know that it was
y ella ya sabía que no colaba eh se que
n't valid so it stayed like that you
no había colado pues se quedó así usted
had understood what you just said to the
había entendido lo que acaba de decir a
lady because you would have to
señora porque es que tendría que volver
watch it again for a minute 43 and and listen to it very
a ver un minuto 43 y y escucharlo muy
carefully and and I think that I wouldn't go back
Atentamente y y creo que no me volvería
that I wouldn't find out either eh you
que tampoco me enteraría eh ustedes
have understood eh
habéis entendido eh
you have understood what the hell she
usted habéis entendido qué [__] es lo
said but it wasn't I get up in
que ha dicho pero no fue me levanto por
the morning and you I have decided that because it
la mañana y vos He decidido que porque
happened and I'm going to do it it wasn't a
se ha pasado y voy a hacerlo no fue una
morning discussion it was an after
discusión matinal fue un después to lo
what you wanted if you give it to me I'll give it to you if I
que te di la gana si me lo das yo te si
want it to you I'll do a thousand to you Ah so here
quiero Te te te hago mil Ah o sea aquí
Loli what I would be saying again is the
Loli lo que estaría volviendo a decir lo
same thing that she said privately to de Troya
mismo que le dijo por privado a de Troya
that she herself later denied in
que luego ella misma desmintió en un en
the chat of the live broadcast of de Troya when
el chat del directo de Troya cuando
later shortly before the live broadcast And that
después poco antes del directo Y eso
although she wanted to delete it but I
aunque ella lo ha querido borrar pero yo
already  I had
ya lo tenía
captured these screenshots one by one
capturado están Las capturas una por una
of all the ones she sent me to see which one she
de todas las que me manda para ver cuál
puts in her live and shows that. She
pone en su directo y enseña eso ella
thought they were going to come back if not,
pensaba que iban a volver si no no lo
she doesn't do it, I mean,
hace ella o sea
okay, I think I'm understanding it, okay, I'll
vale creo que lo estoy entendiendo vale
explain, you thought, I thought that this
os explico pensaban pensaba que ese
procedure was to have that paper in the
trámite era para tener ese papel en el
live, she doesn't do it and it's been
directo no lo hace y está
in conversations since the morning
e en conversaciones desde por la mañana
shortly before the live, that's when
poco antes del directo es cuando se hace
the transfer is made. I translate for you solely and
el traspaso os traduzco única y
exclusively for the live. Only
exclusivamente para el directo Solo que
since it had already been leaked there was no going back.
como ya se había calado no hubo retorno
The only time I'm going to talk to see the
la única vez que voy a hablar a ver la
translation that I understand is the
traducción que yo entiendo es la
following one, let's see if you understand it the
siguiente a ver si ustedes lo entendéis
same as me.
igual que yo
eh, the other day in the ard
eh el otro día en el directo de ard
Troya live, ard de Troya said something that she
Troya ard de Troya contó una cosa que la
told and Loli then denied it in the
contó y Loli luego la desmintió en el
chat. What happened was
chat qué es lo que pasó lo que pasó fue
that Loli told de Troyas something
que Loli le contó una cosa a de troyas
privately that Loli surely
por privado que seguramente Loli se la
made up or nuanced it in her own way, okay, she
inventó o la matizó a su manera vale la
interpreted it in her own way, okay, but it
interpretó a su manera Vale pero no
wouldn't be entirely true, at least not
sería una verdad del todo por lo menos
entirely, okay, at least one  true
del todo vale por lo menos una verdad
completely completely completely I think it wasn't
del todo del todo del todo yo creo que
okay
no era vale
and then the thing is that
e entonces la La Movida es que
when det trya tells it that when
cuando al det trya lo cuenta que cuando
Peppa returns the 500 bucks to Loli
Peppa le devuelve los 500 pavos a Loli
Loli gives her a visa for 1000
Loli le hace un visum de 1000
okay Loli appears in Troya's AR chat
vale aparece Loli en el chat de AR de
and denies it saying No no that's a
Troya y lo desmiente dice No no eso es
lie that's a lie and from Troya I know that
mentira eso es mentira y de Troya se que
like well you know Of course because it's
así como bueno sabes Claro porque es
like Well if you told it to me
como Bueno si tú me la has contado a mí
of course you told it to me in private and
claro me la has contado en privado y
now when I'm telling it in
ahora cuando yo lo estoy contando en
public she's telling me no because
público me está diciendo que no porque
surely she told it to me in private and
seguramente me las contado en privado y
you made it up in private Okay
te las inventado en privado Vale
so the question is
entonces la cuestión es que
what she's trying to fix now La
lo que está queriendo arreglar ahora La
la la Loli I think she's
la la Loli esto yo creo que se lo está
making this up as she goes along I
inventando sobre la marcha yo
personally think that she's
personalmente creo que esto se lo está
making this up as she goes along to
inventando con sobre la marcha para
answer me okay what she's
contestarme a mí vale lo que está
saying is that in the morning she did
diciendo es que por la mañana ella sí
have that argument with Peppa that
que tuvo esa discusión con Peppa de que
Peppa was telling her that she wanted to
Peppa le estaba diciendo que le quería
return the 500 and that Loli said if you
devolver los 500 y que Loli le dijo si
give me back the 500  I'll give you 1000
me devuelves los 500 te doy 1000
so what Loli is saying is
entonces lo que está diciendo Loli es
that Peppa returned the 500 to have
que Peppa le devolvió los 500 para tener
the screenshot to prove on live, okay? Hey
la captura que demostrar en el directo
look, I returned it But
vale Oye mira lo lo he devuelto Pero
because Peppa thought that there were a thousand
porque Peppa pensaba que venían mil de
returns coming and then she didn't give them to her
vueltas que luego pues no se los dio
because she already saw through her, that's what
porque ya la caló eso es lo que entiendo
I understand that this lady is trying to say here. I
yo que está queriendo decir aquí la la
mean, it's not true that she
señora esta O sea que no es verdad que
gave her the 1000 but that Peppa did
le llegó a dar los 1000 pero que Peppa
return the 500 thinking that she was going to
si le devuelve los 500 pensando que iba
receive 1000 in return and that's why she
a recibir 1000 A cambio y por eso lo
did it and to have the screenshot or translator.
hizo y para tener la captura o traductor
Yes, she says that, of course, I mean what she's
Sí dice eso claro o sea lo que lo que se
making up on the fly because she's
está inventando sobre la marcha porque
making this up on the
esto se lo está inventando sobre la
fly to answer me. Of course,
marcha para contestarme a mí Claro
because I'm telling her. Here, well,
porque yo le estoy diciendo Aquí bueno
Peppa made it up. I mean,
que la Peppa se la inventado O sea la
Loli made this up in private with Ar
Loli se inventó esto en privado con ar
de Troya, she made it up and when she saw that
de Troya se lo inventó y cuando vio que
Ar de Troya said it on live,
ar de Troya lo suelta en directo pues
then she appears in the chat running,
entonces aparece por el chat corriendo
you, you, that this is a lie. And
tú tu tú que esto es una mentira Y
then what she does here is eat
entonces aquí lo que hace pues comer
chocolate  eat chocolate or you listen to them
chocolate comer chocolate o las escuchas
elsewhere, to someone else and she
en otra parte a otra persona y ella se
joins in, she makes up stories and things like that
se acopla se inventa cuentos y cosas así
okay And I'm completely sure
vale Y yo estoy completamente seguro de
that Loli makes up a lot of things about
que Loli se inventa muchas cosas sobre
Peppa and about okay This is the same cli
Peppa y sobre vale Este es el mismo cli
No here Lor is watching us to see what he
No aquí lor nos está mirando a ver queé
tells us now to me forgive me but I
nos dice ahora a mí perdonadme pero yo
don't see it I see it wrong I think that this
no lo veo lo veo mal yo creo que esto
more than what is on Twitter would be seen I don't know I think that the
más que está de Twitter se vería No sé
two
yo creo que a las dos compañías de
telephone companies that I
teléfono que
work with I think this clip should be
manejo Creo que este clip se le tendría
sent eh here she is inciting
que hacer llegar eh aquí está incitando
people
a la gente
ole
ole
because I pay them by bank and I don't know what
porque yo las pago por banco y yo no sé
telephony has on the other side to
lo que tiene telefonía al otro lado para
listen to this on a channel eh I don't know about
escuchar esto en en un canal eh No sé de
people and what they have to have to be
personas y que tienen que tener para
able to reach a channel and solar what we
poder llegar a un canal y solar esto que
are going to listen to Eva
vamos a escuchar Eva
Eva listen listen Look this is the most
Eva escucha escucha Mira esto es lo más
bante thing that I have heard in a long
bante que he escuchado yo en mucho
time I understood that that they
tiempo entend eso
make the deposit that same day or
eso que hacen el ingreso ese mismo día o
the next day luckily unfortunately
al día sigui por suerte por desgracia
many bank books pass through my
pasan muchas cartillas bancarias por mis
hands at the end of the month and I see what
manos al cabo del mes y yo veo lo que
these people charge for aid I am not
cobra esta gente de ayudas no me estoy
making it up eh  the girl is saying here
inventando eh lo está diciendo aquí la
eh but now you will see how she explains
chica eh pero ahora veréis cómoo explica
the plot of what these people do how she
la trama de que hace esta gente cómo la
explains it but let's go into details Look And it
explica pero vamos con detalles Mira Y
makes me ashamed I am ashamed of what I
me da vergüenza me da vergüenza lo que
see that they collect aid
veo que cobran de ayudas
and that sen lech they have the income while
e que seún lech haen el ingreso mientras
we listen to her and I read you I am going to the beach
la escuchamos y os Leo me voy a la playa
because I have not gone
porque no he ido
because I found this and I have already
porque lo encontrado esto y ya he
wanted to open directly in nothing that same
querido abrir directo en nada ese mismo
day or the next day they take out all the
día o al día siguiente sacan todo el
money in full they put it in another
dinero íntegro lo meten en otra cuenta
unmonitored account because Claro the moment
no vigilada porque Claro en el momento
they see that they are spending
en el que viesen que se están gastando
300 or 400 on telephony they take away the
300 o 400 en telefonía les quitaban las
aid then eh I have seen how they
ayudas entonces eh yo he visto como lo
take it from one account put it in another
sacan de una cuenta la meten en otra
name of another person who is the one who is
nombre de otra persona que es por la que
charged with the telephone bill and they
le pasan la factura de la telefonía y
have 100 lines in all the lines
tienen 100 líneas en todas las líneas
with Smartphone of the top of the range that there is
con Smartphone del tope de gama que haya
at that time and then you see that they are
en ese momento y luego ves que les están
giving them aid for the house for water
dando ayudas para la casa para el agua
for electricity they pay for school they
para la luz des pagan el colegio les
give them medicines they have
regalan los medicamentos tienen
priority at the doctor eh they give them
prioridad en en el médico eh les les dan
the weekly shopping and  they are spending
la compra semanal y se están gastando
300 and 400 euros on high-end phones, it's amazing to
300 y 400 eur en teléfonos de alta gama
me, oh my God, eh. The more
a mí me madre madre mía eh Yo es que
I hear it, the more I'm shocked, it's
contra má Lo escucho yo más flipada me
not just hearing it and saying, I
quedo no es escucharlo y decir Me
love the measuring stick of these people, it
encanta la vara de medir de esta gente
's like they are
no que es como que se escandalizan
really shocked by some things but there are others
muchísimo por unas cosas pero hay otras
that seem more normal to them in
que les parecen como más normales en la
life, right? I mean, they haven't been shocked to
vida no O sea no se han escandalizado de
defend the sentence of a
defender la sentencia de un abusador de
child abuser, no, they haven't been shocked to
menores no no se han escandalizado de
defend it and say, well, the judges were
defenderla y decir bueno los jueces se
wrong, well, it
equivoc
was a false accusation, well, the
bueno era una denuncia falsa bueno la
victim may have settled with
víctima a lo mejor se ha arreglado con
the aggressor, no, not about those things, no, they haven't been
con el agresor no no de esas cosas no no
shocked, okay, they are shocked
se han escandalizado vale se escandaliza
that alas says that there are people who receive
de que alas diga que hay gente que cobra
payments from the state and then buy
pagas del estado y luego se compran
expensive phones. No, no, it's not that I can
teléfonos caros No no es que cont se
hear it against it, I put it praise, I'm left with that,
escucha contra lo pongo loa me quedo eso
how, well, what you're
có cómo pues pues lo que estás
hearing are conjectures and privacy,
escuchando conjeturas y privacidad
conjectures and Ugh, really, because she is, she
conjeturas y Uf de verdad porque ella es
says that it happens, well, yes,
que ella dice que pasa bueno si es que
all the  head When I see those things but
to la cabeza Cuando veo esas cosas pero
this is what we talk about it is a job that burns
de esto se habla es un trabajo que quema
a lot eh Because it is a
muchísimo eh Porque es una presión
continuous pressure and it is a continuous pressure that
continua y es una presión continua que
I am on the beach of those above on
estoy en la playa de los de arriba por
one side and the client on the other you are
un lado y del cliente por otro tú estás
in the middle and you feel continuous pressure
en el medio y sientes presión continua
from both sides Okay so in the
por las dos partes Vale entonces al
end psychologically that a
final psicológicamente quea mucho
lot, a lot, I
muchísimo o
mean working in telephony which is not to
sea trabajar en telefonía que por no
say any, a lot of work when
decir ningú una quema muchísimo que
someone comes to buy a cell phone it
venga alguien a comprarse un móvil te
burns you the most and making a contract
quema lo más grande y hacer un contrato
is let's go no more what will
es vamos ya no va más de qué trabajará
the lady work to be the one who is so much of
la señora para ser la que está tanto de
help and everything how hard I really
ayudas et de todo qué fuerte de verdad
tell you pu of any saleswoman I mean
digo pu de cualquier dependienta O sea
if she has to accept the financing, I mean
si te tiene que aceptar la financiación
the other day when I went to buy
yo yo el otro día cuando fui a comprarme
the phone and I financed it, I mean instead of
el teléfono e lo financi o sea en vez de
paying for it all at once, I put it Hey well
pagarlo de golpe pues lo puse Oye pues
charge it the Apple option no and and and he
cóbrela la opción Apple no y y y me
asked me Well I don't know what I don't know what he
pidió Pues no sé qu no sé que que me
asked me I think he asked me for
pidió creo que me pidió
some of the exercises of the
algún de los ejercicios de los
quarters or something like that, a salesperson
trimestres o algo así un dependiente
Of course of course to me forgive me but I don't
Claro claro a mí perdonadme pero yo no
see it it's the mother of God another part
lo veo es loo madre de Dios otra parte
now we see, it's a big problem, eh, it's
ahora vemos pues es un buen marrón eh es
a big problem, eh, it's a big problem, eh, Loli, the
un buen marrón eh es un buen eh Loli la
complaint is not presented in court,
denuncia no se presentan los juzgados
okay, declared in contempt, she has a
vale declarada en Rebeldía tiene una
lawsuit to which she has not appeared, the one we
demanda a la que no se ha personado la
are asking for
que le estamos pidiendo
15,000 has a complaint from Joana
15000 tiene una querella de la Joana
Morilla to whom she has not appeared either, no
morilla a la que tampoco se ha personado
problem, okay, but eh, eh, what a problem
sin problema vale pero eh eh vaya marrón
with Anne who has given her opinion on the
al Anne que ha opinado sobre las
payments, for me it would be me, for me, yes, it
paguitas yo para mí sería yo para mí sí
's a big problem because the one who takes
es un buen marrón porque el que coge
this, for you, a big problem is
esto para ti un buen marrón es el
chocolate, the one that gives you allergies, that's a problem,
chocolate el que te da alergia ese es un
but brown, brown, brown, brown,
marrón pero marrón marrón marrón marrón
for example, now the bad thing he says, Hey, what is
por ejemplo ahora lo mal dice Oye qué es
this, what's going on, seriously, you know, all those
esto qué pasa en serio sais Todos esos
movements to the companies and and I don't know, I
movimientos a las compañías y y no sé O
mean, and she's calling her followers,
sea que y está llamando a sus seguidores
thank goodness she has 100, she's calling
Menos mal que tiene 100 está llamando a
her followers to go and boycott
sus seguidores a a que vayan a boicotear
the business where she works, acne, I mean,
el negocio donde trabaja al acne o sea
look at the harassment and Seriously, no, it's
fijaros el acoso y En serio que no que
not from Telephones Come on, Come on, yes, it
no es de Teléfonos Dale que Dale que sí
is a company that sells cell phones and
que es una compañía de que vende móvil y
makes phone contracts as if Oh, I
hace contratos de teléfono como si Ah yo
am, but it's  I don't want to name
soy pero es que no quiero nombrar a
any because I don't know exactly who she
ninguna porque no me sé exactamente la
is because if you knew to
es la que es porque si lo supieras para
take the clip and receive hundreds and
[__] el clip y que recibieran cientos y
hundreds of clips from this lady saying that
cientos de clip de esta señora diciendo
eh but mm because this this what
eso que eh pero mm porque esto esto que
this lady is saying is not
está diciendo esta señora es no es
normal it's not normal it seems to me that
normal no es normal a mí me parece que
the one who is not very normal is you Loli
la que no eres muy normal eres tú Loli
okay but it's a super personal opinion
vale pero es una opinión super personal
eh Maybe I'm wrong what this
eh A lo mejor me equivoco lo que esta
lady is saying is not normal it's not
señora está diciendo no es normal no es
normal she already
normal ya os
pays you it's not normal it's being said about every single one of that she
paga no es normal está diciéndose acadas
knows if a person is
de de que sabe si a una persona se se
helped thato It seems to me that she's referring to
ayudan queo Me parece que se refiere a
the people who come from I'll say it again
la gente que viene de vuelvo a decirlo
that Spain helps them the government helps
que España le ayuda el gobierno ayuda a
those people and I think that maybe she's
esa gente y creo que al igual pues se
referring to those people Eh J you
está refiriendo a esa gente Eh J la has
got her Loli you got her she also
pillado Loli la has pillado que también
says that there's an engine of people who pass them
dice que hay un motor de gente que pase
pass them through their hands and and knows all
las pasan por las manos y y sabe todos
the movements this is the best but
los movimientos esto es la leche pero
what a shame I don't understand what she
que leche Es que no entiendo lo que lo
's trying to do is that she's
que está queriendo es que se está
trying to act like the very very very
queriendo haer como la muy muy muy
indignant no and she's trying like
indignada no y está intentando como
sell it you know but in reality you don't
venderlo s sabes pero en realidad no
know what you're outraged about that
sabe de lo que se está indignado de qué
a saleswoman goes through your
de que una dependienta pase por sus
hands eh the requirements that they ask
manos eh los requisitos que le pidan a
people to finance a phone that is
la gente para financiar un teléfono que
taken out or a contract itself not for
se saque de o un contrato mismo no para
the contract you to sign up for a
el contrato tú para darte de alta en una
phone line they also ask you for things
línea de teléfono también te piden cosas
of course they go through your hands ID they go through
claro pasan por tus manos dni pasan por
your
tus manos sabes es que no no no no sé
hands you know it's that no no no I don't know what it is What's the outrage is that no I'm not understanding What's the outrage And the anarchy how stupid is eh I mean what person more more more stupid eh that they take it out one day and put it
eh que se lo sacan un día y lo meten en
somewhere else to deceive whoever is
otro sitio para para engañar a a quien a
collecting aid so that they don't get
quien cobra es ayuda para que no los
caught I'm freaking out But I
pillen yo lo estoy flipando Pero yo lo
'm freaking out with the people who play
estoy flipando con la gente que hace las
tricks to collect aid I
triquiñuelas para cobrar ayudas Te
feel like I want to run away What
siento como para echar a correr Qué
a shame this 35 like I want to
sinvergüenza esto 35 como para echar a
run away Loli that's me Oh I've
correr Loli eso es yo Ah es que yo lo he
seen it and I've frozen that I've
visto y me he quedado congelada que se
frozen eh I mean he's
ha quedado congelada eh o sea se se ha
really outraged  has been
indignado muchísimo se ha quedado
frozen well well well
congelados bueno bueno bueno se han
data has been taken And it hasn't been legally
sacado datos Y no han sido legalmente
through where it should be but
por la por donde tienen que ser pero
how are they going to take out data that isn't
cómo se van a sacar datos que no sean
legally Lolis if she's telling you that
legalmente Lolis si te está diciendo que
the cards go through her hands
por su manos pasan las
daughter That's what happens ignorant
cartillas hija Es que eso pasa ignorante
what p more ignorant What more ignorant people No
qué p más ignorantes Qué personas más No
but apart is that she is doing it you
pero aparte es que la se está haciendo
know Ho I have been frozen but
la sabes Ho Me he quedado congelada pero
what are you going to stay frozen Loli
de qué te vas a quedar Tú congelada Loli
with what you have seen your eyes what are
con lo que tú han visto tus ojos de qué
you going to be surprised about at this stage of
te vas a asombrar tú a estas alturas de
life if you have had friendship with
la vida si has tenido amistad con la
Peppa when she did the
Peppa cuando hizo lo de los
240 if you hang out with the ard of
240 si te juntas con el ard de
Troy what are you going to be frozen about
Troya de qué te va a quedar Tú congelada
when you hang out with those people I have
cuando te juntas con esa gente Me he
been frozen I have been astonished astonished
quedado congelada Me he quedado atónita
that labra aid of the
atónita que labre ayuda de la
Independence and things like that of the
Independencia y cosas así de la
dependency u u how frozen the law of
dependencia u u qué congelada la ley de
dependency they help you and they can
la dependencia te ayudan y te pueden
but the law of dependency although
pero la ley de la dependencia aunque
she sees that you are You are going to make a
ella vea que tú estás Te vas a hacer una
telephone line and sees that you have an
línea de teléfono y vea que tienes un
income she can't know that that
ingreso ella no puede saber que ese
income has been transferred to an account in someone
ingreso lo has pasado a una cuenta a
else's name  person and on top of that
nombre de otra persona y que encima lo
you do it And you pass that phone number to
haces Y pasas ese teléfono a nombre de
another name the other person's account to
otra la cuenta de la otra persona para
avoid you not getting help It's that it is that it is
evadirte de que no te denes ayuda Es que
But how can she not see it if she
es que es es Pero cómo no lo va a ver si
has to register it has to do with her
le tiene que dar de alta tiene que ver
complying with the she says verbally that they
que cumpla los ella dice verbalmente que
pass around many cards where they receive
que pasan muchas cartillas donde cogan
help and those people the government
una ayuda y esa gente el gobierno le
helps them with medicines, food, paying
ayuda a medicamentos a comer a pagar el
rent, a lot of things and that
alquiler a un montón de cosas y que esa
help that they give them the money that they take
ayuda que le dan el dinero que van cogen
and withdraw goes to another account in someone
y la sacan se va a otra cuenta nombre de
else's name and through the other account in someone
otra persona y por la otra cuenta nombre
else's name they pass around the cell phone the
de otra persona se pasan el móvil el
cell phone of 300 a month, 300 high-end,
móvil de 300 mensuales de 300 de alta
a mobility or
gama un movilidad o
or she doesn't even know what she's been outraged about
o no sabe ni de lo que se ha indignado
okay look and this clip is very
vale mira y este clip pues viene muy a
relevant with this This is a parody okay
cuento con esto Esto es una parodia vale
eh I don't know if it's the same person who
eh No sé si es la misma persona que
runs the Twitter account okay
lleva la cuenta de Twitter esta vale
But this is a parody it's a person
Pero esto es una parodia es una persona
who is dedicated to disguising themselves as us
que se dedica a disfrazarse de nosotros
and doing like parodies it hasn't worked out for me two
y hace como parodias no me ha salido dos
or three times and this one has happened to me before I
o tres veces y esta me ha sido antes
say Hey look well a  a little bit to the
digo Oye mira pues Viene un poco muy a
point not with what with what we're
cuento no con lo que con lo que estamos
seeing not with the super indignation of
viendo no con la la super indignación de
these people when they start pretending Uy
esta gente cuando se ponen a fingir Uy
uy uy I'm outraged by this eh
uy uy qu me he indignado con esto eh a
dogs have to be educated and
los perros hay que educarlos y
socialized in a way that not
socializarlos de una forma en la que no
everything is always rosy and
todo Siempre es de color de rosas y
fun and if the dog suddenly grabs
divertido y si el perro de repente coge
open the shelf and starts
abre la estantería y se pone a
trying to eat the
intentarse comer los productos de
cleaning products that can end its own
limpieza eso puede acabar con su propia
life This doesn't mean that you have to
vida Esto no significa que tengas que
physically harm the animal but you do have to
hacerle un daño físico al animal pero sí
educate it and punish it
que tienes que educarle y castigarle
to protect it from itself and from
para protegerle a él de sí mismo y a los
others as well but cl what type of
demás también pero cl a qué tipo de
Education are you referring to let's see if
Educación se está refiriendo a ver si
jav cl beyond to take photos and videos let's
jav cl más all para hacer fotos y vídeos
see This is a debate about whether the dog
a ver Esto es un debate de si el perro
can be touched or not, it
se le puede dar un toque o no se le
can be touched eh sincerely
puede dar un toque eh sinceramente yo
what I think is that it depends, it depends,
ahí lo que opino es que depende depende
I It depends if we can give a touch to
yo Depende si podemos darle un toque a
a dog so that it is doing its
un perro para está la tan haciendo su
role uy
papel uy
uy How did you say it depends Javi uy
uy Cómo que has dicho depende Javi uy
uy educate it says Javi oliveira u Ja
uy educarlo dice Javi oliveira u Ja
oliveira depends never  never Javi
oliveira depende jamás jamás Javi
Oliveira under no circumstances got into her
oliveira bajo ningún concepto metía en
drama eh got into her
su metía en su drama eh metía en su
drama Eh This is very this is very heavy
drama Eh Esto es muy esto es muy heavy
eh Very heavy eh Ugh this is very heavy eh
eh Muy heavy eh Uf esto es muy heavy eh
her thing That's privacy this is very
lo de ella Eso es privacidad esto es muy
heavy you never
heavy
punish a dog never eh
jamás se castiga a un perro jamás eh
never use negative reinforcement eh
jamás se utiliza el refuerzo negativo eh
that associates something it does wrong with something
que asocie algo que hace mal con algo
that can happen to it worse not something negative
que le puede pasar peor no algo negativo
but with positive reinforcement the
sino con un refuerzo positivo la
education of dogs of animals
educación de los perros de los animales
is based on positive reinforcement okay it is
se basa en el refuerzo positivo vale
locked up to addar it is
está encerrado para adadar está
provoking the to the and now she how
provocando al al al y ahora ella como
she educates her dog she and her
ella educa a su perro ella y sus
followers older than she is already
seguidoras mayor que ya le está
showing her teeth you are
enseñando los dientes
not going to touch a cable the others
no me vas a tocar un cable losotros
argue if a lot this one or the little ones take
riñes si mucho esta o los pequeños coe
a bottle you put water on it and you make it
una botella le pones agua y le haces
smack the snout in the
chuch el hocico en la
face shut up okay And if you want to how to
cara se call vale Y si quieres como
do it as punishment you take a
hacerle como castigo coges una goma de
hair tie and put it on it when you what
pelo y se la pones cuando tú lo que le
the other one told her eh she does she does smack
dijo la otra eh le hace le hace chuchu
on its snout you don't put it in its mouth and a
en el hocico no pones en la boca y una
hair tie on its snout  so that he
goma del pelo en el hocico para que se
shuts up when she sees that he can't
calle cuando ella vea que el hocico no
move his snout, they stop barking, man. I
lo puede mover dejan de ladrar hombre Yo
don't know that, eh. No, I don't know that, eh. It's going very well.
no sé eso eh No yo no sé eso eh va muy
I'll tell you tricks that will work for you
bien Yo te digo trucos que te van ir
because the German step, tricks that work
bien porque el paso alem trucos que van
very
muy
well, tricks that work very well, trick that
bien trucos que van muy bien truco que
works very well, family. I can't.
van muy bien familia Yo no puedo